Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America: Records of Locals WAG.234
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Records of TWU Local 100 (New York City), 1931-1978.
  - Fact Finding Committee (II), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fact Finding Committee: General, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fact Finding Committee, Oct 14, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fact Finding Committee (I), Oct 28, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fact Finding Committee (II), Oct 28, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fact Finding Committee, Oct 29, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fact Finding Committee, Nov 4, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fact Finding Committee (I), Nov 8, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fact Finding Committee (II), Nov 8, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fact Finding Committee, Nov 13, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fact Finding Committee, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fairway Bus Corp., 1939 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fact Finding Committee, 1942, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Fact Finding Committee, 1969, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Field Days, 1945-1948 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1931-1936 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1937 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co. (I), 1938 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co. (II), 1938 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co. (I), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co. (II), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1941 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1944 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co. (I), 1945 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co. (II), 1945 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1947 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1948-1953 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1954-1956 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Fifth Ave Coach Co., 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co., 1963-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Heath and Welfare Fund, undated, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Heath and Welfare Fund (I), 1958 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Heath and Welfare Fund (II), 1958 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Heath and Welfare Fund, 1959-1964 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Pensions, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Pensions, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Pensions, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Co.: Stock Fight, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Fighting Fund, 1946, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Fighting Fund, 1954-1968 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Finance Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Finance Committee, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Finances, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Finances, 1939-1942 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Finances, 1948-1952 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Finances, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Finances, 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Finances, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Finances, 1966-1971 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Finances: Audit Reports, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Finances: Reports, 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Finances: Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Finances: Reports, 1941-1942 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Finances: Reports, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Finances: Reports, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Finances: Reports, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Finances: Reports, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Finances: Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Finances: Reports, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Finances: Reports, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Finances: Reports, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Finances: Reports, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Finances: Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Finances: Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Finances: Victory Tax, 1942-1943 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Financially Speaking, 1952-1953 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Financial Practices of CIO Unions, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Fines Imposed on Local 100 Members, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Fitzsimon, James, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Five Cent Fare, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Fordham Bus Corp., 1937 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Fordham Bus Corp., 1941-1942, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Forge, Maurice, 1949-1950 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Form Letters, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Forty Hour Week (I), 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Forty Hour Week (II), 1951 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Forty Hour Week, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Forty Hour Week: Conference, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Four Hour Pay Claim, 1956, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Free Labor Fund Collection, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Gilmartin, Damiel: Expenses, 1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Goldberg, Arthur, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Gray Line Motor Tours, Inc., 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Gray Line Motor Tours, Inc., 1941, 1945, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Greater New York CIO Council, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1953-1956 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Greater New York Industrial Union Council, CIO, 1940-1942 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Green Bus Lines, Inc., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Greyhound Lines, 1939, 1940-1947 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Grievances, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Grievances, 1939, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Grievances, 1942-1943 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Grievances, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Grievances, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Grievances, 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Grievances (I), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Grievances (II), 1955 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Grievances, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Grievances, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Grievances, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Grievances, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Grievances, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Grievances, 1963-1969 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Grievances, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Grievances: Board of Transportation, 1949-1951 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Grievances: Board of Transportation, 1952-1953 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Grogan, William, 1941-1943, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Guinan, Matthew, 1953, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Guinan, Matthew, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Hannaberry, Joseph, 1958-1960 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Harlem Transit Committee, undated, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Hate Mail, 1941, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Hate Mail, 1950, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Hate Mail, 1956-1960 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Hate Mail, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Hate Mail: Bus Strike, 1952-1953 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Health and Welfare Fund, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Health and Benefit Trust, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Herald Tribune, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Histadrut, 1954-1960 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Hogan Testimonial Dinner, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Holdings, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Holy Name Society, 1954-1955, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Honest Ballot Association, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Hospital Strike, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Housing, 1953-1955 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Hudson Transit Lines, Inc, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Impartial Transit Chairman, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - IND: General, 1938-1945 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - IND: General, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - IND: General, 1952-1954 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - IND: General, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - IND: General, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - IND: Run Schedules, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - IND: Station Dept., 1950-1953 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Independent Subway System, 1935-1937 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Independent Subway System, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Independent Subway System, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Independent Subway System: Election, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO, 1958-1961 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Insurance, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Insurance, 1954-1964 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Insurance Claims, 1940-1944 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - IRT: General, undated, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - IRT: General, 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - IRT: General, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - IRT: General, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - IRT: General, 1941-1943 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - IRT: General, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - IRT: General, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - IRT: General, 1952-1955 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - IRT: General, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - IRT: General, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - %"Beakie" Assault, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - IRT - BMT Pension, 1956-1962 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - IRT: Car Equipment Dept., 1938-1940 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - IRT: Chief Engineers Dept. Sections, 1937-1940 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - IRT: Correspondence, General, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - IRT: Car Maintenance Dept., 1950-1954 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - IRT: Correspondence, General, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - IRT: Correspondnece - General A - D, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - IRT: Correspondnece - General E - H, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - IRT: Correspondnece - General I - M, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - IRT: Correspondnece - General N - Q, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - IRT: Correspondnece - General R - Z, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - IRT: Credit Union, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - IRT: Delinquents, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - IRT: Investigation re: Anti-Communist Dissidents, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - IRT: Financial, 1936, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - IRT: Meetings with Management, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - IRT: Members - General, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - IRT: Motive Power Department, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - IRT: Motormen, 1938-1939, 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - IRT: Pension Board: General, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - IRT: Pension Board: General, 1936-1937 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - IRT: Pension Board: General, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - IRT: Pension Board: General, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - IRT: Pension Board: General, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - IRT: Pension Board: General, 1942-1949 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Pension Board: Financial Statements, 1937-1939 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Pension Board: Financial Statements, 1940-1941 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - IRT: Seniority (1926), 1940 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - IRT: Sick Leave, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - IRT: Station Department, 1944-1946 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - IRT: Station Department, 1948-1951 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - IRT: Station Department, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - IRT: Termination Reports, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - IRT: Towermen, 1949-1951 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - IRT: Transportation Dept., 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - IRT: Transportation Dept., 1956 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - International Association of Machinists, Jan 1936-Aug 1936 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - International Association of Machinists, Sep 1936-Dec 1936 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - International Association of Machinists, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - International Employees union, 1957-1959 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Investigating Committee (Internal), 1948 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Irish Aid: Fitt Luncheon, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Israel, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., Jan 1940-Jul, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., Aug 1940-Dec, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., 1951-1966 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Jay- Vee Bus Co., 1956 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Joint Committee on Transit, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Joint Committee on Transit, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Joint Executive Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Joint Executive Committee, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Joint Executive Committee, 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Joint Executive Committee, 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Joint Executive Committee: Attendance, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Joint Executive Committee, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Joint transportation Committee, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Kent Avenue Power Plant, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Keyserling Report, 1965, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Kheel, Theodore, 1949-1952 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Kheel, Theodore, 1953-1955 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Kheel, Theodore, 1956-1959 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Kheel, Theodore, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Kheel, Theodore, 1965-1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - King, Martin Luther, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Kirrane, William, 1962-1967 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Klein, Michael, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Korean Conflict: Sgt. O'Reilly, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Labor Advisory Committee on Puerto Rican Affairs, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Labor Day Parade, 1959-1963 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Labor - Management Committees, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Labor Relations (NYC), 1941-1945 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Ladies Auxiliary, 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Ladies Auxiliary, 1939-1945 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Layoffs, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Leave of Absence, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Legal Counsel, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Legislative, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Legislative, 1938-1941 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Legislative, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Legislative, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Legislative, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Legislative, 1945-1949 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Legislative, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Legislative, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Legislative, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Legislative, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Legislative (I), 1956 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Legislative (II), 1956 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Legislative (I), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Legislative (II), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Legislative, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Legislative, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Legislative, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Legislative, 1964-1967 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Legislative, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Legislative, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Committee, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Legislative: Correspondence, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Legislative: Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Legislative: Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Legislative: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Legislative: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Legislative: Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Liberty Coach, Inc., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Transit Company, Inc., 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - List of Shops, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Loans, 1950-1953 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Loans, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Long Beach Bus Company, Inc., 1938-1944 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Loyalty File, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Lynch, Josie, 1948-1956 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Lynch, Josie, 1957-1965 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Mackell, Senator Thomas J., 1959 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - MacMahon, Arthur: Article, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Mahedy, Patrick, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Maintenance Dept., 1962 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Maintenance of Way Division, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Maintenance of Way Division, 1950-1953 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Maintenance of Way Division, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Maintenance of Way Division, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Maintenance of Way Division, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Maintenance of Way Division, 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Maintenance of Way Division, 1962-1966 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - MABSTOA, 1962-1963 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - MABSTOA, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - MABSTOA, 1965-1967 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - MABSTOA, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - MABSTOA, 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - MABSTOA: Benefits, 1961-1963 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - MABSTOA: Health and Welfare, 1963-1967 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Manhattan Bus Co., 1957-1964 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Marcantonio, V., 1935, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Marchi - Russo Bill, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - March of Dimes, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - March of Dimes, 1954-1959 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Mass Meeting, Jan 22, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Mass Meeting, Dec 4, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Mayflower Coach Corp., 1956 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Mayor's Advisory Board, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Mayor's Advisory Transit Committee (I), 1946 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Mayor's Advisory Transit Committee (II), 1946 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mayor's Committee on Management, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Mayor's Special Transit Commission (40 Hour Week), 1951 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Mayor's Transit Labor Committee, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - McCarthy, Senator Joseph, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - McLaren, Wilbur, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - McNicholas Case, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Medical Disqualification, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Medical Disqualification, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Medical Disqualification, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Medical Plan, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Medical Plan, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Medical Plan, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Medical Plan, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Medical Plan, 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Medical Plan, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Medical Plan, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Medical Plan, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Medical Plan (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Medical Plan: Continental Assurance Company, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Medical Plan: Health Benefit Trust, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P, 1949-1951 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P, 1952-1954 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P., 1961 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P, 1963-1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P. Cases (I), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P. Cases (II), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P.: Claims, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P.: Claims, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P.: Complaints, 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P.: Complaints, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P.: Complaints, 1956-1960 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Medical Plan: H.I.P.: Praise Letters, 1954, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Medical Plan: Vote, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Meetings with Management (misc.), 1954-1959 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Membership Cards, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Membership Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Membership Data (TA), 1956 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Merger: AFL-CIO, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Mid-City Coach Corp, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Military Service, 1954, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Military Service Men's welfare Committee, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Miner, Paul, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Mitchell-Brooks Bill, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - A Transit Bill, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Motive Power Dept., 1941 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Motormen, 1948-1949, 1955, 1964-1969 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Motormen: Disqualified, 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jun 28, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jul 6, 1956-Jul 9, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jul 10, 1956-Jul 11, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jul 12, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jul 13, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jul 17, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jul 24, 1956-Jul 26, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Motormen: Transit Authority Trial, Jul 27, 1956-Jul 30, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Motormen's Benevolent Assn., 1955-1958 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - MBA: Merger, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - MBA: NLRB Case, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - MBA: Strike (I), 1956 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - MBA: Strike (II), 1956 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - MBA: Strike, Dec 1957 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - MBA: Strike Clippings, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - MBA: Strike Clippings, Dec 1957 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - MBA: Strike Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Motormen's Division, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - N.A.P.A.N., 1963, 1967-1970 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Nassau-Suffolk CIO Council, 1954-1956 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1956-1960 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - National Labor Relationships Board (Includes Non-Communist Affadavits), 1951 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - National Labor Relationships Board, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - National Labor Relationships Board: Religion and Labor Foundation, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - National Labor Relationships Board: War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Negro Labor Committee, 1937, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - New Members, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Newsletters: Other Organizations, 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Guild, 1953-1955 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - New York Bus Tours, Inc., 1956 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1957-1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - New York City Central Labor Council: Hospital and Medical Care Committee, 1961-1965 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - New York City CIO Council, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - New York City CIO Council, 1951-1954 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - New York City CIO Council, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - New York City CIO Council: Community Service Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - New York City Council, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - New York City: Dept. of Labor, 1954-1956, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - New York City: Dept. of Welfare, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - New York City: Dept. of Welfare, 1953-1958 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - New York City: Municipal Transit Workers, Local 380, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1937 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1938 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1939 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1940 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1941 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1942 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1943 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1944 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1946 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1948 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1951-1952 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1953-1957 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp., 1962 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp.: Camp Sheeran, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp.: Negro Employees, ca.1944 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - New York City Omnibus Corp.: Sections, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 6)